<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Projects xmlns="http://schemas.neptuo.com/xsd/neptuo-website-projects.xsd">
  <Project>
    <Name>Solution Runner</Name>
    <Type>desktop</Type>
    <Description>Keyboard-only designed application for simple and fast opening of Visual Studio solution files.</Description>
    <Text>
      <p>
        Keyboard-only designed application for simple and fast opening of Visual Studio solution files. 
        Configuration takes single folder where to look for *.sln files with the option to set prefered Visual Studio version installed on your computer and global (Windows wide) shortcut.
      </p>
      <p>
        After setting required configuration, main window will open. Here you can filter solution files from your hard drive and manage favourite ones. 
        By pressing enter, you run a new instance of selected Visual Studio version with the selected solution.
      </p>
      <p>
        When global hotkey is set, the application is only minimized after opening the solution. So, to update it must first kill it from process list.
      </p>
      <p>
        To start the application after sign in to the Windows, simple create shortcut in startup folder. We are currentling implementing this as feature, along with minimized startup.
      </p>
    </Text>
    <LocalUrl>solutionrunner</LocalUrl>
    <ProjectUrl>https://github.com/neptuo/Productivity.SolutionRunner</ProjectUrl>
    <DownloadUrl>http://apps.neptuo.com/solution-runner</DownloadUrl>
    <Images>
      <Additional>~/Content/Images/Projects/solution-runner-01.png</Additional>
      <Additional>~/Content/Images/Projects/solution-runner-02.png</Additional>
      <Additional>~/Content/Images/Projects/solution-runner-03.png</Additional>
      <Additional>~/Content/Images/Projects/solution-runner-04.png</Additional>
    </Images>

    <Version>
      <Name>v1.6.2</Name>
      <Description>Fix showing a directory in the list when directory with dot in a name is added.</Description>
    </Version>
    <Version>
      <Name>v1.6.3</Name>
      <Description>Fix crashes caused by IO exception while enumerating new directory.</Description>
      <Description>Add support for VS2017 which has different installation path format.</Description>
    </Version>
    <Version>
      <Name>v1.6.1</Name>
      <Description>Changing tray-icon when initializing and displaying intermediate progress bar on task bar.</Description>
      <Description>Fix missing file after moving it with parent directory.</Description>
      <Description>Fix hiding main window after loosing focus if opened by tray-icon.</Description>
      <Description>Fix reseting main window state and position after opening using tray-icon.</Description>
    </Version>
    <Version>
      <Name>v1.6</Name>
      <Description>Added support for counting application and file statistics with classic pie chart view.</Description>
      <Description>Searching is now instant. Removed delay between typing and actual searching.</Description>
      <Description>Added help popup for a first time setup.</Description>
      <Description>Added support for defining custom initial window position.</Description>
      <Description>Added option for displaying tray-icon. Clicking a tray-icon brings a window to front.</Description>
      <Description>File system is scanned in the background. It is also reloaded only when source directory is changed, not on every configuration save.</Description>
      <Description>Improved mode with no hotkey. Application is shown on the task bar and doesn't close after running application.</Description>
      <Description>Added tooltips containing full path for solution files and applications.</Description>
      <Description>Added Ctrl+C and Ctrl+Shift+C commands for copying application path and file path.</Description>
      <Description>Added hover effect for applications and files.</Description>
    </Version>
    <Version>
      <Name>v1.5</Name>
      <Description>Added support for starting after login to the Windows.</Description>
      <Description>Added message displaying current application status (initializing, searching, 'nothing found', etc).</Description>
      <Description>Added options for shortening display path to found solution files. It can whole path, directory path or last directory name.</Description>
      <Description>Fix: Missing favorite items after deleting all text.</Description>
    </Version>
    <Version>
      <Name>v1.4</Name>
      <Description>Added support for custom application defined in the configuration window.</Description>
      <Description>Added configuration option to enable auto selecting Visual Studio version according to the solution file version.</Description>
      <Description>Fix: Duplicated entries after renaming directory.</Description>
    </Version>
    <Version>
      <Name>v1.3</Name>
      <Description>Double click on the application starts new instance without file.</Description>
      <Description>Added support for Home and End navigation keys in the list of solution files.</Description>
      <Description>Added support for hiding/closing main window after loosing focus/deactivating.</Description>
      <Description>Dropped throtling delay when showing pinned files for empty search.</Description>
      <Description>Added support for saving last used application as prefered.</Description>
      <Description>Added detection of single running instance.</Description>
      <Description>Fix: Double click on item opens the file like pressing enter.</Description>
      <Description>Fix: Color of a file path in the selected item.</Description>
    </Version>
    <Version>
      <Name>v1.2</Name>
      <Description>Extend searching in contains mode to support space separated tokens that are matched in the whole solution path.</Description>
    </Version>
    <Version>
      <Name>v1.1</Name>
      <Description>Configuration property for suggestion count.</Description>
      <Description>Configuration property for searching by 'StartsWith' or 'Contains'.</Description>
      <Description>Added command line parameter '--hidden' for starting application hidden.</Description>
      <Description>Configuration property whether to save or not last searched phrase.</Description>
      <Description>Fix: Selecting first suggested item when this one is the only one.</Description>
    </Version>
    <Version>
      <Name>v1.0</Name>
      <Description>Favourite solution list.</Description>
      <Description>Global hotkey.</Description>
    </Version>
  </Project>
</Projects>
